if he is kind hello if she is
если он добрый здравствуйте если она
Hello What are you discussing today I’m from the
Здравствуйте Что сегодня обсуждаете Я из
city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from Lord
города Хмельницкий Вы откуда Господи
Popik You think I don’t know you I
Попик Ты думаешь я тебя не знаю я тебя
don’t know you maybe that’s why I imagine, well you
не знаю может потому я представи ну ты
may not know me Lord that’s why I
меня можешь не знать Господи поэтому я
introduced the city of wort look There is such a thing if
представ горо сусла смотри Есть такое
I  I want to ask a Person I
вот если я хочу Человека спросить Я
introduce myself where I’m from and therefore I
представляюсь откуда я и поэтому
ask where he’s from We’ve
спрашиваю откуда он Мы здесь с тобой уже
probably been talking here for the fifth time already, I don’t remember you,
раз пятый наверно общаемся тебя не помню
well, that’s
ну
not what I’m claiming to be remembered for
не это не претендую на звание чтобы меня
discuss Let's not be interested
бесполезно обсуждать Давайте неинтересно
Let's better ask your
Давай лучше твой
question, how do you feel about the pogrom
вопрос как относитесь к погрома
in Makhachkala yesterday? Well, how did your
Махачкале вчера Ну как ваша
chain achieve its goal? What did the chain do, what did the chain do? Yes, it
цепна добилась своего А что пна сделала
started pogroms, it
что цпти на сделала Да подняла погромы
started an uprising. Wait, what
подняла востание Подождите что что
did the TsPSO do? For example, I just can’t
сделала цпсо Вот например я просто не
imagine if, for example, they write in
представляю если например пишут во
France that in  A plane flies over Paris from
Франции что в Париж пролетает самолёт из
Tel Aviv and the French are going to destroy the
тель-авива и французы идут громить
airport. Well, this is a
аэропорт А ну да это же ведь
Muslim area, yes Stop Stop, and that people from Israel
мусульманский район да Стоп Стоп а что в
are not allowed to fly into a Muslim area, they
мусульманский район нельзя прилетать
can, but
людям из Израиля можно можно но только
that’s the only way. It must
это же мо Надо же определённым образом
be presented correctly in a certain way. Yes, what, how
преподнести правильно Да как что как
if I don’t know, go to the Telegram
если я не знаю вот Зайди в Telegram
channel because they presented it, well, that’s what I’m
канал так как преподнесли ну вот что я
saying. Go to the Telegram channel and read
говорю Зайди в Telegram канал и почитай
how they presented it before, so
как они пред ещё как преподнесли так
say, you said that it’s a bird, what’s
скажи вот ты же сказал что это птино что
here? I don’t understand what a bird should do
зде Я не понимаю что должна сделать
for these people  let's run Who
птино чтобы вот люди побежали Кому
owns the Telegram channel Good morning
принадлежит Telegram канал Доброе утро
Makhachka
махачка
not morning Dagestan Yes, yours say that
не утро Дагестан Да вот ваши говорят что
this is the Ukrainian TsPSO For example, what did the
это украинское цпсо Вот например что это
Ukrainian TsPSO do How to force
украинское цпсо сделало Как заставить
people in Dagestan to go smash the airport,
людей в Дагестане пойти громить аэропорт
this is real How to force Muslims
вот реально Как заставить мусульманов
to go
идти
Muslim
мусуль
SMU why For example in Tatarstan That's
СМУ почему Например в Татарстане Вот
why in Tatarstan  no one ran to
почему в Татарстане никто не побежал
destroy the airfield Yes, to Bashkartastan
громить аэродром Да в башкартастан
because it’s not
потому что там не
so much what they call them, but in
настолько как их называют-то что в
Tatarstan it’s not so much that they’re not so
Татарстане не настолько что там не такие
radical in some Ukrainian center,
радикальные в какой-то украинской цпти
well, interesting No, well, the Ukrainian chain
ну интересно Не ну украинская цепна же
knows where to push Well, okay, just
знает куда давить Ну хорошо вот просто
look at the cut  this Telegram channel
Смотри сечку это Telegram канал
belonged to this Ponomarev sec I am the
принадлежал этому пономарёву секу я
admin of this channel here I am I confess I am the
админ этого канала вот я я признаюсь я
admin of the telegram channel from Dagestan
админ телеграм-канала ут Дагестана
admin parv Ponomarev Okay, come on, this is
админа парв Пономарёв Хорошо давай это
Rossiyskaya, he said everything, he’s a
Российска говорил он все
runaway liberaha Jew, I know everything
го это беглый либераха еврей знаю Всё
is fine He is a liberaha Jew, how did he liberaha
хорошо Он либераха еврей как он либераха
Jew forced a bunch of Dagestanis  destroy the
еврей заставил кучу дагестанцев громить
airfield, tell me what you need to
аэродром что вот скажи что нужно
write
написать
VNA, I didn’t read what is written there How do
вна я не читал что там написано Откуда
you know what then Maybe they just
ты знаешь что тогда Может тебе просто
put noodles in your ears and they put noodles in my ears,
лапшу на уши навели а мне лапшу на уши
wait, I thought you read and
подожди я думал ты прочитал и
understood well that they told you on TV
понял хороо что тебе в телевизоре
like they wrote VNA  I don’t
сказали типа что там написали вна не
know, I didn’t watch the TV How do you know
знаю я не смотрел теле Откуда ты знаешь
this?
это п
Well, that’s why I adequately refugees from
сдем Ну потому я адекватно беженцы из
Israel did not arrive on this flight,
Израиля этим авиарейса не прилетали
respectively, people
соответственно соответственно людей
were deceived so well, people were deceived. For
обманули так хорошо людей обманули Вот
example, they were deceived by someone who deceived them.
например лю обманули кто их обманул Вот
Look, Tsepna Ponor Yes, through the
смотри цепна понор Да посредством
Telegram channel she wrote that refugees from
Telegram канала написала что беженцы из
Israelis are flying into the Makhachkala airfield
Израиля прилетают в аэродром Махачкалы
What prompted people What prompted people
Что побудило людей Что побудило людей
to destroy the airport that year The
году громить аэропорт в том году То же
same thing, the same Telegram channels also
самое те же самые Telegram каналы также
raised again, then look, I
поднимали ещё раз то смотри то получа я
understand correctly that in Dagestan in the
правильно понимаю что в Дагестане в
Russian Federation, where the
Российской Федерации где действует
Constitution of the Russian Federation is in force, people are not allowed to
Конституция Российской Федерации нельзя
fly  from Israel so No these are
прилетать людям из Израиля так Нет это
your words I didn’t say that well Well
твои слова я этого не сказал хорошо Ну а
what then prompted people to go and destroy the
что тогда людей побудило пойти и громить
airport I can’t understand
аэропорт не могу понять
the presence of supposedly refugees from Israel so I
наличие якобы беженцев из Израиля так я
understand correctly that refugees from
правильно понимаю что беженцам из
Israel cannot fly into the territory it is
Израиля нельзя прилетать на территорию
possible Why is it possible why but
можно Почему можно почему но
only in this  the situation turns out that
только в данной ситуации получается что
if the people are warmed up through the public, then the
если народ подогреть через паблики то
people will naturally begin to
народ начнёт этому естественно
resist this because the most
сопротивляться потому что там наиболее
ideological
идейные
Muslims there support the Palestinians, the
мусульмане поддерживают палестинцев
Palestinians support the Palestinians well. That is,
палестинцев хорошо поддерживают То есть
I understand correctly that you are now
я правильно понимаю что вы сейчас своим
voicing in your speech that Israeli citizens
вот речью озвучить что гражданам Израиля
cannot fly to the territory of Dagestan,
нельзя прилетать на территорию Дагестана
wait because there are  some
подожди потому что там есть какие-то
aggressive Muslims No, not because there are
агрессивные мусульмане Нет не потому что
aggressive Muslims there, but because
там агрессивные мусульмане а потому что
there Muslims were deceived through
там мусульман обманули посредством
publicity, how they were deceived. I ask how
паблика как обманули Я же спрашиваю как
they were deceived, how they were deceived again, I
обманули как обманули ещё раз те
repeat, they said that refugees are arriving.
повторяю сказали что прилетают беженцы
Yes, if only it were true, that’s
Да вот если бы это было правда вот
really good, they’re actually arriving
реально хорошо вот реально прилетают
refugees and the public writes refugees are arriving, they are
беженцы и паблик пишет прилетают беженцы
not deceiving, refugees are actually arriving,
не обманывают реально прилетают беженцы
then everything would be fine, then they would
тогда бы всё нормально было тогда бы и
sort it out. Wait again. That is, the fact
разбирались Подождите ещё раз То есть то
that the plane arrived without refugees is
что самолёт прилетел без беженцев это
normal, but if only, that is. It is not
нормально а если бы то есть Это не
normal, there were no refugees there
нормально там не было беженцев
initially, correct. Well, what if  if they
изначально правильно Ну а если бы они
were that would be so the crowd would come you know so
были что было бы вот толпа пришла знаешь
that it would be until mushrooms grow in your mouth you
чтобы было бы до кабы в рту вырастут
know this saying come on so
грибы знаешь такую поговорку давай так
refugees from Israel can fly to
беженцам из Израиля можно прилетать в
Makhach, probably they can, but what’s the
Махач наверно можно можно да в чём
problem that they wrote on the Telegram channel
проблема что в Telegram канале написали
that there is a plane with refugees from Israel
что что самолёт с беженцами из Израиля
will fly to
прилетит
Makhachkala, what's the problem? Yes, they
Махачкалу в чём проблема Да там же не
wrote there for a reason that there is a plane from
просто так написали что там самолёт из
Israel about You didn't read How they
Израиля про Ты же не читал Как там
wrote there Oh, let's open it Yes, come
написали Ой ну давай откроем Да давай
on Open it, let me have this
Открой давай у меня этот
bookmark Well, then read it I'm not
закладок Ну давай тогда читай я я же не
not you Read where  they wrote there I have
не ты же Прочитай где там написали я
n’t seen anything like this And you have something like this And what did you
такого не видел А ты такого А что ты
see Tell me what you
видел Расскажи что ты
saw Tell me what you saw I’m still looking for
видел Расскажи что ты видел я пока ищу
hearing that in short it’s to organize
слыша что короче это это организовать
everyone’s been writing to me on this channel since
все пишут у меня ещё этот канал ещё с
last year when you had mobilizations
прошлого года когда у вас мобилизацию
like Well, they’re right  they even
типа были Ну они правильно они ещё
organized it back then Yes, this is all
тогда устроили Да вот это вот все весь
this whole movement, and then it was also proven that
этот движ да тогда ещё было доказано что
this is a super Yatina flail and here is a satin flail
это цеп ятина супер да вот цеп сатина
Come to the morning of Dagestan Come on the morning of
Заходи в утро Дагестана Давай утро
Dagestan
Дагестана
Yes,
да
I won’t be surprised if the posts there are already
я не удивлюсь если там посты уже
worn out Come on
потёртые давай
Uh-huh That is, you didn’t even read  I’ve
Угу То есть ты даже не читал не заходил
never been in it. Yes,
никогда Да в него 16
January 16th is also not
января тоже не
the same.
тот
And I can’t go in because it’s a
А я не могу зайти потому что это
closed Telegram channel where it’s
закрытый Telegram канал где
closed.
закрытый
Well, I found only three Telegram channels
Ну я нашёл только три Telegram канала
morning of Dagestan, one is this morning of
утро Дагестана один один это утро
Dagestan, which was conducted for 100 years at lunchtime,
Дагестана который вёлся 100 лет в обед
the second which is not on this at all  topic and the
второй который вообще не по этой теме и
third one says that it is blocked and We
третий написано что он заблокирован и Мы
moved to another one called the basement of
перешли в другой называется подвал
Dagestan bark closed you’re like didn’t read
Дагестана коры закрытый ты типа не читал
I understood you didn’t read the
я понял ты не читал хорошо
question well I can nay uh we
вопрос Могу най э е сре всего че
got together and told the governor to
собрались и губернатору говорили чтобы
evict all the Jews from the district this is also
выселить всех евреев из округа это тоже
morning Dagestan A  here is and about this where
утро Дагестан А вот есть а об этом где
Yes Now I am from your source,
Да Сейчас я вам из твоего источника нет
I’m not on the Russian Telegram channels I’m still a
в Telegram каналах российских Я же всё
monitor I’m a normal source now I
монитор Я же нормальный источник сейчас
’ll tell you straight away Yeah I’m collecting this right
вам прямо вот скажу Угу я такое прямо
now, well, it’s actually strange yes You’re
так сейчас ну вообще странно да Ты
now trying to talk about
сейчас пытаешься рассуждать на темы
people’s Faith  who
Веры людей которые
live as Muslims, I
проживают мусульмане поддерживаю
support people of their own faith in
поддерживают людей своей же веры в
another place where they are killed, they are brutally
другом месте где их убивают жестоко
killed Yes, and accordingly these
убивают Да вот и соответственно у этих
people
людей
have a negative feeling, it is
появляется негатив те
called then when those people
лю называется потом когда те люди
who are representatives of that
которые представители той
us seis neno,
ны сейс нено
you take it, says you didn’t read the morning of
м ты берёшь говорит ты не читал утро
Dagestan to you  they said on TV and
Дагестана тебе сказали по телевизору и
you are broadcasting this Russian Propaganda with your mouth, look,
ты своим ртом транслирует эту российскую
go to the channel chtd
Пропаганду да посмотри зайди канал чтд
is called Yes
называется Да
528,000 subscribers Russian news
528000 подписчиков российский новостной
channel Yes And so the local residents asked for a rally to evict the Jews from
канал Да И вот митинг выселить евреев из
Koch of Circassia Yes,
коча Черкесии попросили местные жители
here is a direct
Да вот тут пря
rally how they communicate with the governor
митинг как они общаются с губернатором
or someone or the head of the Republic  that's all I
или кем или главой Республики это всё я
turned off the sound for you, you can turn off the
тебе звук отключил можешь отключаться
sucker that's it You're a complete zero you don't
[__] всё Ты полный ноль ты не
operate voiced I'm poking you with the facts
оперирует озвучиваешь я тыкаю тебя факты
you go away let's go Balabol they rolled
ты пошёл вон давай всё Балабол раскатали
it out just like a childish damn thing That is, I
его просто по-детски блин То есть я
love the morning the morning of Dagestan the morning of Ma he
люблю утро утро Дагестана утро ма он
couldn't even say the name  channel
даже не мог назвать типа название канала
like yes, in
типа да
short, he didn’t read any of them didn’t
короче он не читал никто из них это не
read the most important question, yes, what needs to
читал самый главный вопрос да что нужно
be told Yes, so that people would go to destroy the
рассказать Да чтобы люди пошли громить
airport, yes, that is, that
аэропорт да то есть что там прилетят
refugees would fly there They were deceived that
беженцы их Обманули что прилетят беженцы
refugees would arrive, well And if the refugees Okay, they deceived And
хорошо А если беженцы Ладно обманули А
if there were real refugees then  that it is necessary
если беженцы реально были то что надо
to destroy the airport and their
громить аэропорт и ихний
plane is a question So Russia, yes Russia
самолёт вопрос Вот и Россия да Россия
no longer controls anything,
уже не контролирует ничего
write on th Telegram directly at once axis VN apok tse
пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through srg org in new ban and even more
нас через срг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
videos I don’t show people at all times I don’t show them
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about the stream Tomu for this purpose shob
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
mi Mali operational link pi right behind the apok
ми Мали оперативний звязок пи прямо за а
there in telegra okm video tezh Tsikava and
пок там в телегра окм видео теж цикава и
Korisna information and mi povinni z you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативний звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши